Izzat Mammadov

Front-End Developer



Personal details



Izzat Mammadov



imamedov388@gmail.com



+994503882464



Baku, Azerbaijan



March 25, 2000

Skills

HTML5 / CSS3 / SCSS / Bootstrap /
JavaScript / jQuery / AJAX /
TypeScript / React.Js / Tailwind CSS /
Redux / Next.Js / Git / GitBash etc.

Languages

Turkish

•••••

English

••••

Hobbies

- Fitness
- Swimming
- Alpinism

Summary

Offering years of progressive experience in owning web-based projects from concept and design through testing, implementation and client updates. Diligent about producing exceptionally clean, strong and secure code. Successful at achieving browser, device and operating system compatibility objectives while satisfying client desires and producing robust, sophisticated designs. I always improve myself and I am open to learning new information.

Employment

Front-End Developer

Apr 2023 - Jan 2024

EA Camp School

- Developed user interfaces for web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and some frameworks.
- Implemented responsive design techniques to ensure websites are optimized for mobile devices.
- Collaborated with back-end developers and designers to create seamless website experiences.
- Tested functionality of front end code across different browsers and platforms.

Front-End Developer

Nov 2022 - Mar 2023

Developia Engineering Academy

- Completed design projects to meet budget, equipment, performance and legal requirements.
- Implemented improvements to boost site performance.
- Assisted in debugging cross-browser compatibility issues.
- Continued self-education and training to keep up with industry changes and trends.

Education

Marketing and Management

2016 - 2020

Azerbaijan Cooperation University

Courses

CELT Colleges

General English

Links

Portfolio: www.github.com/izzatmammadov

Profile: www.linkedin.com/in/izzatmammadov